CHETAN SINDHE

Front End UI Specialist



+(91)974-076-6266

csindhe@gmail.com

06-Aug-1985

Bengaluru

About Me

An avid programmer with prolific knowledge on Javascript possessing pragmatic approach to the real-time problems or requirements. Have been an active player in the innovtion design and implementation with a flair for generating new ideas based on the current project scenarios. Also a quick learner of new skills with an eye for constant evolution in knowledge and continous improvement towards technical expertise thus becoming a strong player in the design and implementation.

Primary Skills

ANGULAR	****
REACT JS	***
JAVASCRIPT	****
Typescript/ES6	****
RXJS OBSERVABLES	****
REDUX	****
BACKBONE JS	***
JAVASCRIPT DESIGN PATTERNS	****

Secondary Skills

HTML, CSS, JQUERY JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT ANGULAR (4+), ANGULAR + REDUX RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN

Education

B.E Mechanical Engineering

Work Experience

Relevant Experience

6 Years 5 Months

UI PROGRAMMER / CONSULTANT Infosys Ltd.

Nov 2017 - Present



11 Years 5 Months

Currently working on Community Portal application based on eCommerce business model for Johnson Controls using Angular 5.0. Have worked on UI/UX requirements and Mobile Responsive requirements for an existing application.

TECH LEAD / UI PROGRAMMER

Tech Mahindra Ltd.

July 2015 - Oct 2017



Actively involved in Innovative Idea Initiative for User Interface for Telia Company. As part of the initiative I used BackboneJS, ReactJS, Angular 2.0/4.0, RxJS and Responsive Web UI over the course of 2 years in order to develop Order Management (ReactJS) and Service Management applications (Angular).

TEAM LEAD / UI PROGRAMMER

Cognizant Ltd.

Oct 2007 - June 2015



Worked in following technologies like Javascript, Jquery, HTML, CSS as part of project requirements. Have also worked on packaged solution like Siebel CRM in Healthcare, ePharma and Telecom. Was instrumental in developing intuitive UI under Siebel OpenUI (Facade pattern) umbrella (OneView Dashboard).